export default  [
    {
        "question": "62 + 63",
        "option1" : "123",
        "option2": "125",
        "option3": "122",
        "option4": "126",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "____ 75 x 9",
        "option1" : "725",
        "option2": "665",
        "option3": "675",
        "option4": "705",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "50 : 10",
        "option1" : "5",
        "option2": "20",
        "option3": "25",
        "option4": "23",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "24 x 15",
        "option1": "260",
        "option2": "220",
        "option3": "320",
        "option4": "360",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "142 + 179",
        "option1": "321",
        "option2": "311",
        "option3": "331",
        "option4": "312",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "123 + 288",
        "option1": "391",
        "option2": "421",
        "option3": "411",
        "option4": "402",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "(23 + 27) - 18",
        "option1": "38",
        "option2": "28",
        "option3": "32",
        "option4": "22",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "(11,7 - 8,9) + (8,2 + 9,9)",
        "option1": "30,9",
        "option2": "20,1",
        "option3": "30,1",
        "option4": "20,9",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "(18,2 - 13,7) + (12 + 11,9) ",
        "option1": "24,4",
        "option2": "34,2",
        "option3": "18,2",
        "option4": "28,4",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "(12:6) + (23 - 12) + (12 x 12)  ",
        "option1": "152",
        "option2": "157",
        "option3": "167",
        "option4": "156",
        "answer": 2
    }
]